[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
[beeps]
[drill whirring]
[speaking Japanese]
[engine turning over]
[tires screeching,
horn honking]
♪ ♪
[laughs]
Whoo!
[retching]
[speaking Japanese]
[sighs]
[upbeat electronic music
playing]
♪ ♪
[glasses clinking]
[speaking Japanese]
♪ ♪
That is a beautiful suit.
Another bottle?
- Of course.
Ohno-san, as I was saying,
I was thinking--
- Zuki-sama.
- Yeah.
[speaking Japanese]
[group laughing]
[person giggles,
indistinct chatter in Japanese]
[light funky music]
♪ ♪
[person singing in Japanese]
[laughter]
[glasses clink]
Be generous.
- Okay.
- [speaking Japanese]
[speaking Japanese]
[laughter]
all: Kanpai.
And while there's
room for improvement--
[speaking Japanese]
[laughter]
You're all doing great.
Thank you.
And a special thank-you
to Club Polina's
number-one girl, Claudine.
[all oohing]
- Thank you, Mama-san.
Claudine, can I get your help
for a minute?
Did you see me
with that big-spending
architect, Ohno-san?
The man buys.
He's coming in again
tomorrow night.
- One of the girls is stealing.
- Are you sure?
Receipts don't match
the inventory.
I'm down a million yen
this month.
What do you think I should do?
[sighs] I mean, find out
who it is, right?
And then confront her.
Yeah, makes sense.
So why are you stealing
from me, Claudine?
Samantha, if half
your customers are here for me,
it's not really stealing,
is it?
I'm just taking my fair cut.
You'll start
paying me back tonight.
Take it out of your pay--it
should take about eight weeks.
Really? You think I'm going
to stick around for that?
You know who owns
half of this club.
You cannot steal their money
and go set up shop
somewhere else.
Go ahead, whistle
for your thugs.
I'll tell them you don't know
how to keep track
of their money.
I'll have the keys to
this place in ten minutes.
You're fired.
Fine.
I'm taking all my clients,
especially
that big-spending architect.
You're going to be fucked
without the money
that I bring.
I'll take my chances.
[serious music]
♪ ♪
[both breathing heavily]
[speaking Korean]
[chuckles]
[speaking Japanese]
[dramatic music]
Dad's 60th is in two months.
Mom's got a big thing planned,
and your presence
is mandatory.
When you called and told Dad
you were thinking
of coming home,
it really hurt him
when you didn't.
This is your chance
to make it up to him, okay?
[bike bell dinging]
And you should actually make
me a tape for once,
because, Joshua, I am
the only person in this world
who actually likes you.
[person speaking Japanese]
- What is he yelling about now?
- We do not know.
Is he still on you about that
Metropolitan Assembly piece?
He made me rewrite it twice,
then reassigned it to Ichihara.
I read your piece about
the traffic-fatality scam.
It's good, Jake-san.
- Thanks, man.
Yeah, I just wish
they hadn't buried it
all the way in the back.
- Really?
You have started
getting bylines,
and you are complaining?
Jake, now.
Hai.
Your piece in this
morning's paper is good.
The last three months,
your work has been excellent.
Thank you, Maruyama-san.
I have what look to be
two big stories.
You tell me which one you want.
Yeah, sure. Okay.
Motorcycle thefts
are way up--
Shinjuku, Asakusa, Shibuya.
A lot of our readers
ride motorcycles, even Baku.
Well, he rides a scooter.
What's the other one?
Dead body found last night
in a pawn shop.
Police think he's a yakuza.
Um, I'll take
the motorcycle story.
Make sure and get a quote
from a cop.
Arigato gozaimasu.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
[lighter clinks]
[lighter clicks closed]
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
[indistinct chatter,
telephones ringing]
Do you also have
a yakuza-related
citizen's complaint to file?
Actually, I'm on a story.
Do you know anything
about motorcycle theft?
You must have me confused
with a real policeman.
[speaking Japanese]
So this is your new position--
organized-crime
consultation department?
How much longer do
you have to stay there
and take that punishment?
I was held
officially responsible
for Miyamoto's death.
So...
I must count myself lucky
I was not fired.
How is your work, Jake?
Good.
Busy.
I'm keeping my nose clean.
As you said,
other crimes to be exposed,
other wrongs to be righted.
Any word on Tozawa?
The same.
You know, he tried to go
to the United States,
then...
nothing.
Have you received anything else
from whoever sent you
that tape?
It's complicated.
I wish I could help you
with your story, Jake.
Well, it was a good excuse
to get you out of prison
for an hour.
[chuckles]
[speaking Japanese]
[all speaking Japanese]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
[door opens]
♪ ♪
[elevator bell dings]
- Hey.
You were right.
This Minekawa Takako
is the shit.
Oh, good.
You know, you could buy
your own music.
With the price
you charge for drinks,
I got to conserve my resources.
So how's business?
- Great.
Is being the big boss
everything you expected?
Just, you know, having
responsibility changes things.
Like what?
Like, I find myself
lecturing my girls
on not showing too much
cleavage and cursing so much.
This is you
we're talking about?
I know, right?
How about you?
Still avoiding the yakuza?
Yeah, still staying
off the sauce.
Actually, the work
I'm doing now,
I can see it make a difference,
like, an actual difference.
That's great.
I'm actually working
on this big story right now--
motorcycle theft.
I was wondering
if you might know anyone
who might know anything?
Oh.
Okay, now we get
to the real reason
you just happened to stop by.
God.
Okay.
Yeah, my...
my body guy in Ayase
might possibly walk a little
in alternative markets--
no guarantees.
Watch yourself.
Don't be stupid.
Don't be stupid--
[snaps fingers]
I'll have to remember that.
Thank you.
[speaking Japanese]
[scoffs]
[chuckles]
[soft music]
[indistinct chatter]
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
[door opens, closes]
[phone beeps off]
[scoffs]
[slurping]
[grunts]
[speaking Japanese]
Eh?
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[tool grinding]
[speaking Japanese]
[grinding slows, stops]
- Samantha.
[tool whirs]
[whirring slows, stops]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Mm...
[chuckles]
[soft music]
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
[door closes]
[upbeat pop music playing]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter, laughter]
[laughing]
[elevator bell dings]
♪ ♪
That's very kind of you.
Is Claudine here?
Claudine has chosen to
pursue other career interests.
[sighs] What a pity.
She was always
a wonderful conversationalist.
To be honest,
good conversation
is the minimum standard
I expect here.
I'm afraid you might have been shortchanged.
Allow me
to personally remedy that.
Another time perhaps.
♪ ♪
I hope to see you soon.
[speaking Japanese]
♪ ♪
[energetic music]
Whoo-hoo!
Hey, hey!
♪ ♪
[engines revving]
[lighter clicks closed]
♪ ♪
Whoo!
[speaking Japanese]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[people speaking Japanese]
[laughter]
[all chattering indistinctly
in Japanese]
[door closes]
[all shouting]
[chuckles]
[laughter]
- Yeah.
[knock at door]
[door opens]
[soft music]
♪ ♪
Your place looks good.
Thanks.
♪ ♪
I'm sorry for not
getting in touch.
Yeah.
I called a lot.
I know.
♪ ♪
I went to your offices.
They said you were
somewhere safe, recovering.
They wouldn't tell me
anything else.
What happened?
♪ ♪
Tell me.
A knife in the stomach.
Oh.
It's okay.
It turns out I have
very hard internal organs.
♪ ♪
[chuckles]
I'm sorry about your friend
and for not doing more.
I'm sorry
for expecting you to.
♪ ♪
Are you taking over
for Kobayashi?
Good.
So you came by to check in?
I came to tell you that
you must rehire Claudine.
Excuse me?
She must work here.
Sato, she stole from me.
She's really fucked me.
This is Oyabun's order.
Tell Ishida-san the last time
that I checked our contract,
as long as he gets his money,
I run the club the way I want.
Samantha,
you need to do this.
Trust me.
You need to hear
what I'm saying.
My club...
my rules.
Thanks for stopping by.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
New batch.
Be honest.
Ooh, you made those?
Last night.
Butter cookies.
[mouth full]
Dude!
You're wasting
your talents here.
I used
a very light maple glaze.
Mmm.
You're a rock star, really.
Don't give
all those away, okay?
Save me some?
- Okay.
- Don't give them all away.
- Sure.
Rock star.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Hello, Mama-san.
Hello, wild child.
♪ ♪
I don't know
what I would have done
if you hadn't hired me.
I knew you'd be
a good hostess.
Club Destiny
was a great place to start.
Better than Club Onyx
you went to next.
[speaking Japanese]
I'm sorry that I left,
just disappeared.
I'm really sorry.
Is this what
those phone messages
were about months ago?
I called you back the next day.
Yeah.
I meant to call you back again.
I'm sorry about that, too.
Thank you.
I was angry,
but that's also
in the past now.
And look at you now, Samantha.
Five years on, your own club.
Good for you.
For you too, Erika-san,
if you'd like.
I need a number-one girl.
I got out for a reason,
you know.
I'll give you half
of all your table charges,
half of every bottle you sell.
[chuckles]
Samantha,
you must be desperate.
[speaking Japanese]
[chuckles awkwardly]
I had no idea.
It was a surprise to me, too.
Just come tonight--
same offer.
Plus, I'll pay for a sitter,
get you a ride home.
The girls are great.
The place is great.
And I trust you.
[laughter]
[speaking Japanese]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
[cell phone ringing]
[beeps]
[dramatic music]
[engine revving]
♪ ♪
[knock at door]
[speaking Japanese]
♪ ♪
[phone ringing]
Moshi moshi.
Ohno-san.
It's Samantha from Club Polina.
[chuckles]
I seem to be
very popular today.
Claudine called me as well.
- Did she?
It seems she has decided
to ply her trade
at a different club.
I see.
Well, I have been seriously
considering your case
and have taken decisive actions
to retain your loyalty,
which is why I have engaged
the most beautiful and charming
woman in all of Tokyo
to dedicate herself tonight
to entertaining you.
This may be true, but it
isn't very modest of you.
I'm--I'm referring
to my good friend Erika.
And it is, I promise you,
quite true.
That's hard to prove.
But I will come in,
and I'll give your place
another try tonight.
I am very pleased
to hear that.
If you agree
to grace my table.
No one else, just you.
[line beeps]
- [grunts softly]
[energetic music]
♪ ♪
Okay.
[camera shutter clicking]
[device beeps, drill whirring]
[suspenseful music]
[both speaking Japanese]
Hey, do you lot know
where Roppongi is?
[both speaking Japanese]
Where the girls and the clubs
and the bars are at?
- [grumbling]
- Uh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
I learned a Japanese song.
- [speaking Japanese]
- It's a famous song.
I bet you know it.
[engine turning over, revving
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
Maybe another time.
[continues singing]
[all speaking Japanese]
Wait a minute.
No, no, no, no, no.
No. I had no idea
that investors were so wicked.
They are.
Okay, what about you?
What are architects
really like?
Me?
Yeah.
[chuckles]
We're confidence men.
We convince our clients
we see the future,
that their building
will look beautiful,
that it will fit
in its setting.
Okay, okay.
You know, I used to work
for a man
who said hostesses sell dreams.
- Hmm.
- I don't think that's true.
So what are you selling?
What am I selling?
A place where confidence men
can come and be honest.
Then, honestly...
this is the best evening
I've had in a long time.
[laughter]
Me too.
I'm so glad.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
[knock at door]
No, Samantha.
It's too much.
You're kidding.
You got Nishikawa-san
to buy more bottles tonight
than he did in a week.
Honestly, I forgot
how good I was.
[chuckles]
And you had fun, too, right?
I did.
Hey, I wanted
to ask you earlier.
Who's your pretty friend?
Polina.
The club's named after her.
Ah.
She died three months ago.
Oh, Samantha, I'm so sorry.
That night I left you
all the voice mails,
that was the night
I found out she died.
I called you because
I didn't have anyone else.
Oh.
So I'm really
glad you're here.
Me too.
[knock at door]
I need a locker,
store some papers.
Help yourself.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
No Saturdays.
Your other girls
can do losers' night.
And I want one night a week
for tai chi.
Fine. I will take
my number-one girl
as many nights
as I can get her.
Sato-san?
Mm-hmm.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
[keys clacking]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[phone dialing]
[modem squealing, whirring]
[cell phone ringing]
Moshi moshi.
It's me.
Would you like to come over?
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Hi.
I saw one of your articles
in yesterday's paper.